Guide to the Sports Memorabilia Collection SC0814
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Sports Memorabilia collection
1898-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University
Spieker, Tod
SC0814
115.5 Linear Feet
Tickets, game programs, schedules, newsletters, pre-season guide books, sport magazines, and other ephemera from college and professional sports.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Tickets, game programs, schedules, newsletters, pre-season guide books, sport magazines, and other ephemera from college and professional sports.
Separated Materials
Stanford football programs, media guides and tickets added to "http://www.oac.cdlib.org/findaid/ark:/13030/c8np26k5">Stanford University, Department of Athletics, Football Collection (SC1185)
Professional sports -- United States.; Football.; Stanford University -- Athletics; College sports -- United States.; Football -- California.; Athletics -- United States.; Stanford University; Spieker, Tod; Stanford University
- Sports Illustrated, Accession ARCH-1998-109
  - Vol.1 No.1 [8/16/1954]; Vol.5 No.21 [11/19/1956]; Vol.6 No.15 [ 4/15/1957]; Vol.13 No.26 [12/26/1960]; Vol.27 No.21 [1/20/1967]; Vol.29 No.20 [11/11/1968]; Vol.30 No.22 [6/2/1969]; Vol.31 No.12 [ 9/15/1969]; Vol.34 No.4 [1/25/1971]; Vol.34 No.11 [3/15/1971]; Vol.35 No.23 [12/6/1971]; Vol.36 No.1 [1/3/1972]; Vol.36 No.4 [1/24/1972]; Vol.36 No.20 [5/15/1972]; Vol.41 No.12 [9/17/1974]; Vol.41 No.25 [12/16/1974]; Vol.42 No.19 [5/12/1975]; Vol.43 No.18 [11/3/1975]; Vol.43 No.21 [1/24/1975]; Vol.45 No.3 [7/19/1976]; Vol.45 No.8 [8/23/1976];Vol.45 No.10 [9/6/1976];Vol.46 No.3 [1/17/1977]; special issue [(2/17)/1977]; Vol.46 No.25 [6/13/1977]; Vol.47 No.10 [9/5/1977]; Vol.47 No.12 [9/19/1977]; Vol.47 No.18 [10/3/1977]; Vol.48 No.3 [1/16/1978]; Vol.48 No.4 [1/12/1978]; Vol.48 No.7 [2/9/1978] (Box 1)
  - Vol.48 No.9 [2/20/1978]; Vol.48 No.10 [2/27/1978];Vol.48 No.12 [3/13/1978]; Vol.48 No.13 [3/20/1978]; Vol.48 No.15 [4/3/1978]; Vol.48 No.21 [5/15/1978]; Vol.48 No.25 [6/12/1978]; Vol.49 No.1 [7/3/1978]; Vol. 49 No.3 [7/17/1978] -Vol.49 No.5 [7/31/1978]; Vol.49 No.11 [9/11/1978]; Vol.49 No.22 [11/27/1978]; Vol.49 No.24 [12/11/1978]; Vol.49 No.25 [12/18/1978]; Vol.50 No.1 [1/8/1979] -Vol.50 No.4 [1/29/1979]; Vol.50 No.7 [2/15/1979]; Vol.50 No.12 [3/19/1979] - Vol.50 No.14 [4/2/1979]; Vol.50 No.21 [5/21/1979]; Vol.50 No.23 [6/4/1979]; Vol.50 No.25 [6/18/1979] - Vol.51 No.5 [7/30/1979]; Vol.51 No.7 [8/13/1979] – Vol.51 No.9 [8/27/1979] (Box 2)
  - Vol.51 No.10 [9/3/1979] - Vol.52 No.14 [3/31/1980] (Box 3)
  - Vol.52 No.15 [4/1/1980] - Vol. 53 No.22 [11/24/1980] (Box 4)
  - Vol.53 No.23 [12/1/1980] - Vol.54 No.3 [1/19/1981]; Vol.54 No.5 [2/2/1981] - Vol. 55 No.4 [7/20/1981]; Vol.55 No.6 [8/3/1981]; Vol.55 No.7 [8/101/1981] (Box 5)
  - Vol.55 No.8 [8/17/1981] - Vol.56 No.11 [3/15/1982] (Box 6)
  - Vol.56 No.12 [3/22/1982] - Vol.57 No.21 [11/15/1982] (Box 7)
  - Vol.57 No.22 [11/22/1982] - Vol.57 No.26 [12/20/1982]; Vol.58 No.2 [1/17/1983]; Vol. 58 No.5 [2/7/1983] - Vol.59 No.6 [8/8/1983] (Box 8)
  - Vol.59 No.7 [8/15/1983] - Vol.60 No.19 [5/7/1984] (Box 9)
  - Vol.60 No.19 [sic] [5/14/1984] - Vol.61 No.4 [7/18/1984]; Vol.61 No.6 [7/30/1984] - Vol.61 No.23 [11/19/1984]; Vol.61 No.27 [12/17/1984]; Vol.61 No.28 [12/24-31/1984] (Box 10)
  - Vol.62 No.1 [1/7/1985] - Vol.63 No.15 [9/30/1985] (Box 11)
  - Vol.63 No.16 [10/7/1985] - Vol.63 No.23 [11/20/1985]; Vol.63 No.26 [12/9/1985] - Vol.64 No.25 [6/23/1986] (Box 12)
  - Vol.64 No.26 [6/30/1986] - Vol.66 No.11 [3/16/1987] (Box 13)
  - Vol.66 No.12 [3/23/1987] - Vol.66 No.26 [6/29/1987]; Vol.67 No.2 [7/13/1987]; Vol.67 No.4 [7/27/1987] - Vol.67 No.8 [8/24/1987]; Vol.67 No.10 [9/7/1987] - Vol.68 No.2 [1/18/1988] (Box 14)
  - Vol.68 No.3 [1/25/1988] - Vol.68 No.6 [2/8/1988]; Vol.68 No.8 [2/22/1988] - Vol.69 No.9 [8/29/1988]; Vol.69 No.11 [9/12/1988] - Vol.69 No.15 [10/3/1988] (Box 15)
  - Vol.69 No.17 [10/17/1988] - Vol.70 No.23 [5/29/1989]; Vol.70 No.25 [6/12/1989] (Box 16)
  - Vol.70 No.26 [6/19/1989] - Vol.71 No.10 [9/4/1989]; Vol.71 No.12 [9/18/1989] – Vol.71 No.26 [12/18/1989]; Vol.72 No.2 [1/15/1990] - Vol.72 No.6 [2/12/1990]; Vol.72 No.8 [2/26/1990] - Vol.72 No.12 [3/26/1990] (Box 17)
  - Vol.72 No.13 [3/28/1990] - Vol.73 No.4 [7/23/1990; Vol.73 No.6 [8/6/1990] - Vol.73 No.9 [8/27/1990]; Vol.73 No.12 [9/17/1990] - Vol.73 No.27 [12/31/1990-1/7/1991] (Box 18)
  - Vol.74 No.1 [1/14/1991] - Vol.75 No.2 [7/8/1991]; Vol.75 No.4 [7/22/1991] - Vol.75 No.21 [11/11/1991] (Box 19)
  - Vol.75 No.22 [11/18/1991] - Vol.77 No.7 [8/17/1992; Vol.77 No.11 [9/14/1991]; Vol.77 No.12 [9/21/1992] (Box 20)
  - Vol.77 No.13 [9/28/1992] - Vol.78 No.9 [3/8/1993]; Vol.78 No.12 [3/29/1993]; Vol.78 No.14 [4/12/1993] - Vol.79 No.8 [8/23/1993]; Vol.79 No.11 [9/13/1993] - Vol.79 No.13 [9/27/1993] (Box 21)
  - Vol.79 No.14 [10/4/1993] - Vol.79 No.18 [11/1/1993]; Vol.79 No.20 [11/15/1993] – Vol.81 No.10 [9/5/1994] (Box 22)
  - Vol.81 No.11 [9/12/1994] - Vol.83 No.3 [7/17/1995] (Box 23)
  - Vol.83 No.4 [7/24/1995] - Vol.83 No.9 [8/28/1995]; Vol.83 No.11 [9/11/1995] - Vol.84 No.12 [3/25/1996] (Box 24)
  - Vol.84 No.13 [4/1/1996] - Vol.85 No.8 [8/19/1996]; Vol.85 No.11 [9/9/1996] - Vol.85 No.24 [12/9/1996] (Box 25)
  - Vol.85 No.25 [12/16/1996] - Vol.87 No.7 [8/18/1997]; Vol.87 No.10 [9/8/1997] - Vol.87 No.12 [9/22/1997] (Box 26)
  - Vol.87 No.13 [9/29/1997] - Vol.88 No.15 [4/13/1998] (Box 27)
- Sports Memorabilia, 1898-2005; Accession ARCH-2000-094
  General note
  Boxes 21 -23 contain Track & field programs, primarily for college events but also including InterAllied Games in France, 1919; Olympic tryouts and games 1928, 1932, 1936, 1952, 1956, 1960, 1968; and USA – USSR meets, 1962, 1964, 1971.
  - Street and Smith Pro Football Magazine, 1966-1979 (Box 1)
  - Street and Smith Pro Football Magazine, 1981-1990 (Box 2)
  - Street and Smith Pro Football Magazine, 1991-1995 (Box 3)
  - Street and Smith Football Magazine – College, 1940-1961 (Box 3)
  - Street and Smith Football Magazine – College, 1962-1974 (Box 4)
  - Street and Smith Football Magazine – College, 1976-1980 (Box 5)
  - Street and Smith Football Magazine – College, 1981-1991 (Box 6)
  - Street and Smith Football Magazine – College, 1992-1997 (Box 7)
  - Sporting News Pro Football Yearbook, 1983, 1986, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Sporting News College Football Yearbook, 1983-1995 (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous football magazines, 1948-1971 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous football magazines, 1972-1982 (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous football magazines, 1982-1995 (Box 10)
  - Illustrated Football Annual, 1931-1949 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous football magazines, 1993-1999 (Box 11)
  - Rose Bowl programs, 1950-1977 (Box 12)
  - Rose Bowl programs, 1978-1994 (Box 13)
  - Pro Log – The NFL Annual, 1972-1990 (Box 14)
  - Pro File – Official NFL Publication, 1975 (Box 14)
  - PRO – Official Magazine of the NFL, 1980, March/April 1983, Nov. 1984 (Box 14)
  - Team NFL – Official Magazine of the NFL, 1991 (Box 14)
  - Kickoff – Official Magazine of the NFL, 1998 (Box 14)
  - California – Stanford Big Game programs, 1930-1963 (Box 15)
  - California Football Magazine/Touchdown Illustrated, 1977-1985 (Box 15)
  - California – Stanford Big Game programs, 1986-1998 (Box 16)
  - Sports Illustrated Sept. 1, 1983; Sept. 4, 1995; and April 20, 1998- July 13, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Sports Illustrated July 20, 1998 – April 12, 1999 (Box 17)
  - Sports Illustrated April 19, 1999 – Dec. 20, 1999 (Box 18)
  - Sports Illustrated Dec 27, 1999 - February 21, 2000 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous magazines (baseball, basketball, misc.), 1948-1963 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous magazines (baseball, basketball, misc.), 1964-1982 (Box 20)
  - Track & field programs, 1888-1932 (Box 21)
  - Track & field programs, 1932-1962 (Box 22)
  - Track & field programs, 1964-1981 (Box 23)
  - College basketball programs, 1938, 1966-1982 (Box 23)
  - College basketball programs, 1983-1997 (Box 24)
  - College basketball programs, 1997-2000 (Box 25)
  - Pro basketball programs, 1957-1975 (Box 25)
  - Harlem Globetrotters souvenir programs, 1955, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Pro basketball magazines, 1959-1972 (Box 25)
  - Basketball magazines, 1976-1977, 1981-1982 (Box 26)
  - Pro basketball guides, 1969-72 (Box 26)
  - College basketball guides, 1951-1975 (Box 26)
  - College football media guides (Pac 10), 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - College football media guides (Pac 10), 1999 (Box 28)
  - NCAA Official Records Book, 1994 (Box 28)
  - Rose Bowl Press Guide, 1995 (Box 28)
  - College football media guides (Pac 10, Notre Dame, Army & Rose Bowl), 1981-1985 (Box 28)
  - College football media guides, 1989-1991 (Box 29)
  - College football media guides (small), 1980-1990 (Box 29)
  - College football media guides (mostly Pac 10 or Pac 8), 1954-79 (Box 30)
  - Pro football media guides, 1995-96 (Box 31)
  - College football media guides, 1949-1991 (Box 32)
  - Sporting News Football Trivia (Box 32)
  - NFL Report, 1983, 1984 (Box 32)
  - Pro football media guides (includes arena football teams), 1978-1983 (Box 33)
  - Sporting News Super Bowl Guide, 1993 (Box 33)
  - Pro football media guides (includes arena football teams), 1979-1980 (Box 34)
  - Sporting News Football Guides, Registers, and Super Bowl Books (Box 34)
  - Pro football media guides (includes arena football teams), 1962-1980 (Box 35)
  - Sporting News Football Guides, Registers, and Super Bowl Books (Box 35)
  - NFL Report 1981, 1982 (Box 35)
  - NFL Record Book, 1971 (Box 35)
  - Pro football media guides (includes arena football teams), 1968-82 (Box 36)
  - Official NFL Record Manuals, 1971-1983 (Box 37)
  - Pro football yearbooks, 1959-1982 (Box 38)
  - Official NFL Record and Fact Books, 1989, 1991, 1994 (Box 38)
  - NFL Post Season Media Guide 1997 (Box 38)
  - Official NCAA Football Guides, 1960-85 (Box 39)
  - Kessler Fan Guides, 1969-1971 (Box 39)
  - Pacific Coast Baseball League Records, 1903-1955 (Box 39)
  - National collegiate Championships, 1969 (Box 39)
  - Sports Chronicle, 1946 (Box 39)
  - World Series Encyclopedia, 1960 (Box 39)
  - Misc. football pamphlets (Box 39)
  - PAC-10 Sports Report, May 1980 – December 1983 (Box 40)
  - National Football Conference Media Information Book 1970 (Box 41)
  - American Football Conference Media Information Book 1970 and 1973 (Box 41)
  - Peristyle – Official Publication of the L.A Coliseum Sports Arena, 1976-78 (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous football programs, 1945-1976 (Box 41)
  - Poling's Football Ratings by Richard Raymond Poling, 1939-46 (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous sports publications 1935-83 (Box 41)
  - Official Football Rules – Spaulding, 1920 (Box 41)
  - Official Football Rules – Spaulding, 1930 (Box 41)
  - Golf publications (mostly tournament programs), 1955-1985 (Box 42)
  - College football media guides (Pac 10), 1981-1982 (Box 42)
  - College football media guides (Pac 10), 1983-1991 (Box 43)
  - College football media guides (Pac 10), 1992-1995 (Box 44)
  - College football programs (mostly PAC-10), 1995-1996 (Box 45)
  - PAC-10 News, 1995-2000 (Box 45)
  - UCLA Bench Warmer, 1976-1988 (Box 46)
  - Sportsmen of the South, 1976-1985 (Box 46)
  - UCLA Bruins Athletic Newsletter, 1984-88 (Box 46)
  - UCLA Sportsline, 1980-81 (Box 46)
  - 1998 UCLA Official Guide for Season Ticket Holders and Boosters (Box 46)
  - UCLA Daily Bruin – special Rose Bowl issue, 1/1/86 (Box 46)
  - PAC-10 football programs, Aug. - Sept. 1997 (Box 46)
  - PAC-10 football programs, Oct. - Nov. 8, 1997 (Box 47)
  - PAC-10 football programs, Nov. 15, 1997 – Sept. 1999 (Box 48)
  - PAC-10 football programs, Oct. 1999 – Nov. 2000 (Box 49)
  - College football programs (mostly Pac 10), 1999-2000 (Box 49)
  - Sports Illustrated, 1998, 1999, Jan. - Aug. 2000 (Box 50)
  - Sports Illustrated, Sept. 2000 – March 2001 (Box 51)
  - NFL Insider 1998-2001 (Box 52)
  - NFL Kickoff '98 (Box 52)
  - NFL & AFL Pro Football Record Books, 1964, 1965, 1966 (Box 52)
  - Official Pro Football Record Books, 1967, 1968 (Box 52)
  - Pro Football Monthly's Who's Who in Football, 1980, 1981 (Box 52)
  - The First Official NFL Trivia Book, 1980 (Box 52)
  - The Second Official NFL Trivia Book, 1982 (Box 52)
  - NFL Man of the Year Award, Press Information Guide, 1971, 1973 (Box 52)
  - NFL Game Day, 1992-1997 (Box 53)
  - World Cup USA 1994 Official Gameday Program (Box 54)
  - Direct TV On Sports, Aug. 2000 and Nov/Dec 2000 (Box 54)
  - The America's Cup Summer, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Twins Magazine, August 1993 [pro baseball team] (Box 54)
  - California Football Media Guide, 2000 (Box 54)
  - Arizona Football Media Guide, 2000 (Box 54)
  - Washington Football, 2000 (Box 54)
  - Notre Dame Football Yearbook, 2000 (Box 54)
  - Dave Campbell's 2000 Texas Football (Box 54)
  - Assorted Stanford basketball programs, 2000-2001 (Box 54)
  - UC Irvine Basketball, 2000-01 (Box 54)
  - Coors Classic Dec. 16, 2000 [college basketball] (Box 54)
  - Stanford University Official Guide for Season Ticket Holders & Boosters, 1998 (Box 54)
  - University of California Official Guide for Season Ticket Holders & Boosters, 1998 (Box 54)
  - Cornell Swimming & Diving Media Guides (Men and Women), 2000-01 (Box 54)
  - Stanford Scorecard, 1981-1999 (Box 54)
  - California Athletic News, 1984-1999 (Box 54)
  - Pro Football Illustrated, 1941-1949 (Box 55)
  - Who's Who in Iowa Football, 1948 (Box 55)
  - Sports Review, 1950 (Box 55)
  - Converse Basketball Yearbook, 1959 (Box 55)
  - Alouettes press guide, 1973 (Box 55)
- Sports Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2006-098
  - Schedules and tickets from Stanford games, 1969-2003; the Pac-10 football and basketball, 1984-2004; UCLA games, 1976-2004; and CAL Berkeley games, 1948-2005 (Box 1)
  - Assorted college football games, 1915-2004; miscellaneous college sports, 1975-2003; Pro football, 1973-2004; and Pro baseball and basketball, 1958-2003 (Box 2)
- Sports Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2006-111
  - 2005: Oregon State @ UCLA; Arizona @ USC; Arkansas @ USC; Sacramento State @ CAL (Box 1)
  - 2004: Iowa @ Arizona State (Box 1)
  - College football programs 1922-1966 (Box 2)
  - Rose Bowl programs 1935-73 (Box 3)
  - Other Bowls and All Star Games programs 1937-99 (Box 3)
  - Big Game (CA v. Stanford) programs 1925-59 (Box 3)
  - East-West Shrine Game programs 1927-84 (Box 3)
  - College Football Guides, 1948-77 (Box 3)
  - NCAA Guide 1898-1947 (Box 3)
  - Pro Football programs 1935-95 (Box 4)
  - Pro Playoff Games 1957-85 (Box 4)
  - Bro Bowls 1960-79 (Box 4)
  - Chicago Tribune All-Star game 1951 (Box 4)
  - March Field All-Stars v. Washington 1944 (Box 4)
  - Pro Football Guides 1964-2002 (Box 4)
  - Pro Football Illustrated 1948 (Box 4)
  - Football Form 1945 (Box 4)
  - Illustrated Football Annual 1935 (Box 4)
  - Baseball World Series Programs, 1947 and 1963 (Box 5)
  - Baseball Yearbooks: SF Giants, 1973, St. Louis Cardinals 1960, Cincinnati Reds 1960 (Box 5)
  - Scorecards (Scorebooks) assorted pro-baseball teams, 1944-85 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous items: 1949 Baseball Register, 1912 Spaulding's Baseball Guide, 1901 Frank Merriwell's Club, 1903 Sports Recap Book, 1923 Championship Records, 1956 Olympic Trials Track Program (Box 5)
  - Pac-10 News 8/21/01 – 12/5/05 (Box 5)
  - Stanford Basketball Programs 2002-2005 [not full coverage] (Box 5)
  - 2001-2002 Washington Basketball Gameday Magazine No. 7-#10 (Box 5)
  - Las Vegas Bowl Media Guide 2001 (Box 5)
  - McCarthy Football Handbook 2004 (Box 5)
  - Athlon Football Magazine, Pac Ten edition 2004 and Pro edition 2004 (Box 5)
  - NCAA Men's Water Polo Championship Dinner Program 2001 (Box 5)
  - Pacific Coast Conference Football Press Book, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Sports Collectors Digest, Issue Number One, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Arena Bowl XV Playoff Football Program 2001 (Box 5)
  - Notre Dame Football Yearbook 2003 (Box 5)
  - NFL Insider Magazine (3 issues) 2002 (Box 5)
  - Swimming/Diving Guides for UCLA 2001, Nebraska 1998 and 1999, USC 1999, Washington 1999 (Box 5)
  - Pac-10 Preseason Basketball Guide 2002/03 (Box 5)
  - UCLA Men's Basketball summer prospectus 2001 (Box 5)
  - California Basketball Guide 2001/02 (Box 5)
  - Stanford Basketball Guide 2001/02 (Box 5)
  - Sports Illustrated issues: January-December 2001 (Box 6)
  - Sports Illustrated issues: January-August 2002 (Box 7)
  - Sports Illustrated issues: September-December 2002 and January-March 2003 (Box 8)
  - Sports Illustrated issues: April-December 2003 and January-April 2004 (Box 9)
  - Sports Illustrated issues: May-September 2004, Nov. 15, 2004, and January-August 2005 (Box 10)
  - Sports Illustrated issues: September-December 2005 (Box 11)
- Sports Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2008-018
  - College Football
    - NCAA Football Guide 2000 and 2004 (Box 8)
    - Programs from Rose Bowl Kickoff Luncheon. Hall of Fame Induction 12/31/02 and 12/31/03 (Box 8)
    - College football media guides: Cal 2001, 2002, 2003; Arizona State 2001, 2002; Arizona 2005; UCLA 2002; Oregon State 2004; Washington 2005; New Orleans Bowl 2005 (Box 8)
    - College football programs Aug. 25-Sept. 29, 2001 (mostly Pac-10) (Box 1)
    - College football programs Sept. 29, 2001-Oct. 26, 2002 (mostly Pac-10) (Box 2)
    - College football programs Nov. 9, 2002-Nov. 15, 2003 (mostly Pac-10) (Box 3)
    - College football programs Sept. 3 - Nov. 13, 2004 (Pac-10) (Box 4)
    - College football programs Sept. 1-Oct. 1, 2005 (Pac-10) (Box 5)
    - College football programs Oct. 8, 2005-Sept. 9, 2006 (Pac-10) (Box 6)
    - College football programs Sept. 15-Nov. 18, 2006 (Pac-10) (Box 7)
    - College football yearbooks: Notre Dame 2000 and 2005, Fresno State 2003 (Box 7)
    - College football media guides: Stanford 2006 and 2007 (Box 7)
    - Rose Bowl Guide 2007 (Box 7)
    - Street and Smith College Football magazine 2002 and 2003 (Box 7)
  - MLB
    - Minor League Scorecards: 1971 Hawaii Islanders (Box 10)
    - Major League Baseball Post Season Programs:
      - ALCS – Baltimore Orioles @ Oakland A's 1974 (Box 10)
      - ALCS – Boston Red Sox @ Oakland A's 1975 (Box 10)
      - World Series – SF Giants vs. Anaheim Angels 2002 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous items: Monte Irwin autographed photo; Lou Boudreau autographed photo; 1970 Kessler Baseball Fan Guide (Box 10)
    - Major League Baseball Scorecards:
      - Oakland A's 1970, 1972, 1973, 1975, 1976, 1977, 1980 (Box 10)
      - California Angels 1970, 1975, 1976 (Box 10)
      - SF Giants 1971, 1972, 1973, 1974, 1975, 1976, 1977, 1978, 1979, 1980, 1981, 1982 (Box 10)
      - LA Dodgers 1972, 1974, 1976 (Box 10)
      - Chicago Cubs 1991 (Box 10)
      - Milwaukee Brewers 1991 (Box 10)
      - Baltimore Orioles 1992 (Box 10)
      - Boston Red Sox 1992 (Box 10)
      - Detroit Tigers 1999 (Box 10)
  - NFL
    - Pro football media guides: St. Louis Rams 2002, Arizona Cardinals 2002, SF 49ers 2003-2004, Miami dolphins 2007. (Box 1)
    - Pro football pubs: Pro Football Hall of Fame Yearbook 2007, Canadian Football League magazine 2005, Philadelphia Eagles Yearbook 2002. (Box 1)
    - Tailgating Times magazine: Steelers vs. 49ers 11-17-2003; Cardinals vs. 49ers 12-7-2003 (Box 1)
    - Team photos: LA Rams 1978; SF 49ers 2003, 2006; Cowboys 1994 (Box 1)
    - Autographed photo of Bob Libby of the Dallas Cowboys (Box 1)
    - "The Next Generation" celebrating the 60th 49ers season, 2005; "A Reason to Believe" 49ers 2006 season, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous college baseball programs and guides (Southern Cal 1970, 1981; Stanford 1984 and 1998) (Box 7)
  - Tailgate magazine (recipe booklet) 2002 (Box 8)
  - Bruin Blue Official Newspaper of UCLA Athletics Aug. 2005 and Sept. 2007 (Box 8)
  - College Basketball programs:
    - Stanford @ Cal 2/26/54 (Box 8)
    - UCLA @ Cal 3/2/57 (Box 8)
    - Olympic Club @ College of the Pacific 2/1/58 (Box 8)
    - San Jose St. @ USF 2/28/58 (Box 8)
    - Double header: Cal @ USC with Washington @ UCLA 1/2/60 (Box 8)
    - USC @ Cal 2/12/60 (Box 8)
    - Cal @ USF 12/7/63 (Box 8)
    - Stanford @ USF 12/5/64 (Box 8)
    - Cal @ USF 12/3/65 (Box 8)
    - UCS @ USF 1/28/66 (Box 8)
    - Stanford @ USF 12/1/66 (Box 8)
    - Duke @ UCLA 12/10/66 (Box 8)
    - Washington @ UCLA 1/6/68 (Box 8)
    - Columbia @ Harvard 1/23/74 (Box 8)
    - Prairie View and Portland @ Oregon St. 11/22 and 11/25/2004 (Box 8)
    - Arizona @ Cal 2/13/94 (Box 8)
  - College Basketball post-season programs: 1979 NCAA Finals; NIT Playoff game 3/13/66; Pac-10 Tournament 1989; 1989 NCAA Finals; 1995 NCAA West Regional; 1995 NCAA Finals; 1997 NCAA West Regional; 2004 SEC Tournament (Box 8)
  - Other basketball programs: Russian-American National All-Star Game in San Francisco April 23, 1966; 1964 Redwood Empire Invitational Basketball Tournament (8 high school teams, Healdsburg, CA) (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous items: 2003-04 Oregon State Winter Sports poster; 2000 Pac-10 Track and Field Championships at U of Oregon (Box 8)
  - Swimming Items:
    - International Swimming Hall of Fame Yearbook 2007 (Box 9)
    - Stanford Clara International Swim Meet 2002, 2006 (Box 9)
    - USA vs. Australia Swim Meet @ Indianapolis 2003 (Box 9)
    - National Championship Swim Meet at Stanford 2004 (Box 9)
    - 55 Year Reunion and Tribute to George Haines 6/29/06 (Box 9)
    - National High School swimming rule book 1998-99 (Box 9)
    - Collegiate Media Guides for Swim Teams at Stanford, 1992-93 and 2002-2003; Cal 1997-98 and 2002-03; USC 2000-2006; UCLA 2002-03, 2003-04, 2005-06; Arizona 2004-05 and 2005-06; Cornell 2005-06 and 2007-08. (Box 9)
    - Team photo: UCLA women 2005-06 (Box 9)
    - Autographed photo of Natalie Coughlin 2004 (Box 9)
  - Water Polo, Collegiate:
    - Media Guides for UCLA, 2001, 2002, 2004, 2006; University of the Pacific, 2001, 2002; USC, 2001, 2002; Stanford 2003, 2004, 2005, 2006, 2007. (Box 9)
    - NCAA Men's Championship Program 1995 and 2003 (Box 9)
    - NCAA Women's Championship Program 2001 (Box 9)
    - USA Men's and Women's Pre-Olympic Competition 2000 (Box 9)
    - Programs from single games, Pac-10 miscellaneous, 2002-05 (Box 9)
    - USA Water Polo Magazine Summer 2004 (Box 9)
    - USA Men's and Women's Water Polo guide 2000 (Box 9)
    - NCAA rule book 1998 (Box 9)
    - Stanford NCAA Championship Men's Team 2002, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 9)
    - Autographed photo of NCAA Championship Cal team 2006 (Box 9)
  - NBA Playoff Programs:
    - St. Louis Hawks @ SF Warriors 1967 (Box 11)
    - Philadelphia 76ers @ SF Warriors 1967 (Box 11)
    - St. Louis Hawks @ SF Warriors 1968 (Box 11)
    - Milwaukee Bucks @ GS Warriors 1972 (Box 11)
    - Milwaukee Bucks @ GS Warriors 1973 (Box 11)
    - Seattle Supersonics @ GS Warriors 1975 (Box 11)
    - Chicago Bulls @ GW Warriors 1975 (Box 11)
    - Washington Bullets @ GS Warriors 1975 (Box 11)
    - Detroit Pistons @ GS Warriors 1976 (Box 11)
    - Phoenix Suns @ GS Warriors 1976 (Box 11)
    - Detroit Pistons @ GS Warriors 1977 (Box 11)
    - LA Lakers @ GS Warriors 1977 (Box 11)
    - Chicago Bulls @ LA Lakers 1991 (Box 11)
    - Utah Jazz @ GS Warriors (Box 11)
  - NBA All Star Programs: 1967 at San Francisco, 1974 at Seattle (Box 11)
  - NBA regular season programs: 1956 Minneapolis Lakers vs. Philadelphia Warriors @ San Francisco; 1959 Cincinnati Royals @ Minneapolis Lakers (Box 11)
  - NBA Media guide for LA Lakers 1972-73 (Box 11)
  - Major League Baseball All Star Programs:
    - 1980 @ Los Angeles (Box 11)
    - 1984 @ San Francisco (Box 11)
  - Major League Baseball Yearbooks:
    - LA Dodgers 1973, 1974 (Box 11)
    - S. F. Giants 1975, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Oakland A's 1976, 1983 (Box 11)
  - World Series 2002 - SF Giants vs. Anaheim Angels, Oct. 20, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous Items:
    - Bill Russell photo (Box 11)
    - Jerry West photos, autographed (Box 11)
    - 2005 Lelands / Joshua Gibson - 1950-51 Reprint Sample (Box 11)